-Do you --
Do you have a minute,
Mayor Mamdani?
-Of course. But first, I need
to address this nor'easter.
Quick, get out your phone.
I need to send an urgent message
about this dangerous storm.
-Ready, sir.
Rain
Avoid
-Shelter in place, y'all. Mm.
-Hey, uh, perfect.
Now, Mr. Mayor,
there's someone here to see you.
-What? What reckless lunatic
would travel to see me
in this kind of weather?
That's crazy.
-Your best friend.
Wonderful.
- Oh, yes.
Mr. President,
you're here...again.
-Of course I am.
I miss my Day One,
Zoran Mamdani.
Of course, for some reason
that no one can figure out,
I really, really like you.
-That's -- That's very kind.
But wouldn't you rather be
in DC?
We're in the middle of El Niño.
-Oh, El Niño.
We don't like big storms,
especially when they're
in Spanish.
-Yeah, well, let's just pray
that it passes quickly.
-Oh, I don't pray at all.
I don't go to church
on Christmas,
"nor'easter."
Boom!
Somehow, when I'm with you,
I'm just firing
on all cylinders.
Maybe it's
because we're both from Queens.
-I know.
Isn't it funny to think
I could have grown up
in one of your
apartment buildings in Queens?
-Not with that last name.
-Mr. President,
I'm actually very busy,
and I assume you are, too.
-Wrong!
I just love hanging out
with you.
We're like one of those
unlikely animal friendships,
like when a tiger gets together
with a baby goat.
When I see stuff like that,
I want to text it to you and say,
"This could be us,
but you playin'."
Is that timely?
Do people still say that?
Anyway, how are you?
-I'm great.
It was a great summer.
I'm still riding high
on that Knicks championship.
You know, I checked that out.
I went to one game,
ruined the vibe,
and then dipped.
-By the way, I took your advice
on Iran for my speech at the UN.
Is it the "U-N" or "un"?
-"U-N."
Wait, so you said we need
to work towards a ceasefire
and sustain peace?
-Oh, I could have sworn
you told me to say,
"I'm going to annihilate you!"
-Yeah,
I don't think that was me.
-Maybe I dreamed it.
You're in most of my dreams.
I call you "Mam-dreamy."
Pick me. Choose me. Love me.
Anyway...
It's been a crazy week.
I kicked out the press
and, uh, uh, hung out
with the president of China --
Xi -- Xi.
And, yeah, I went brunet.
It's fall.
Mr. President, I-I-I just, um --
-There was
this crazy AI stuff, too.
I just had dinner
with Sam Altman, Elon Musk,
and Mark Zuckerberg.
And it made me think, "Wow,
RFK Jr.'s probably right
about those vaccines."
I mean, the tizz in that room.
You know what that's short for,
right -- the tizz?
Have you heard that?
Maybe take a break from the AI
and start working
on "A-eye contact," right?
Some of these guys --
it's crazy.
-Well,
that was a crazy thing to say,
but it's getting late.
I have important work
tomorrow, okay?
I have to go to Bushwick
and give ketamine
to underprivileged bisexuals.
-I don't know what
any of those words mean.
-Excuse me, Mr. President.
Someone is here to see you.
-What reckless lunatic
would travel to see me
in this kind of weather?
-It's your assistant,
Natalie Harp.
-Hi.
Hi, Mr. President. Hi.
-Natalie, I didn't realize
you were in New York.
-Oh, I wasn't.
I ran here from DC,
"Weapons"-style.
-I, uh, came in case
you needed anything,
because, um...
♪ Baby boy,
you've been on my mind ♪
-Beyoncé.
Isn't she great?
She's like the girl
from "Obsession," but blonde.
No.
No..
No, I'm kidding,
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
I'm totally normal.
I'm totally n-normal.
Anyways, nice to meet you,
Mayor Mamdani.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I'm just going to
give him some...
If you hurt him, I will end you.
Okay, fine, fine!
Wow.
-Well, uh, Mr. President,
I really do
have to get back to work.
-Oh, come on, Z-bag!
ZZ Top.
"Zenon: The Zequel."
Don't make me go back there.
I don't want to go.
The judges keep telling me no.
Mitch McConnell keeps
giving me the peace sign,
whatever the hell that means.
Please let me stay here
with you.
-Okay.
Only if you give us $21 billion
for a housing project in Queens.
-Are you out of your mind?
-What if I follow you back
on Instagram?
-It's a done deal.
-And live from New York,
it's "Saturday Night"!
Musical
Host
-Ladies and gentlemen,
Jalen Brunson!
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
It's great to be here.
I'm very excited.
You guys can probably tell
by my voice and face.
But, tonight, I'm going to
approach hosting
the same way
I approach a Knicks Finals game.
So the first three quarters
of the show
are going to be godawful.
The last sketch
is going to be amazing.
Anyway -- Anyway,
I had a pretty good summer.
I helped the Knicks
win the NBA championship.
By now, you've all heard me
talk about it,
but you haven't heard me
sing about it.
And, obviously,
I'm not going to.
But, look, the new season is
just a couple weeks away,
and I got to say,
it's going to be pretty cool
to be back
in Madison Square Garden.
Looking around like,
"Wow, just a few months ago,
this was the exact spot
where Taylor and Travis
got married."
And I would say
the most satisfying part
of winning the title
is thinking about all the people
who doubted me along the way.
And tonight, I finally
get to get some closure.
I invited one
of my biggest doubters here
to apologize to my face --
Stephen A. Smith.
You know what?
Let me say this,
Jalen Brunson.
I am man enough
to admit that I was wrong
when
the New York Knickerbockers
signed you,
and I did not think
that you were the answer,
nor did I believe that
you could deliver
the team's first championship
since 1973,
when I was only 5 years old.
-Sorry, Stephen. Uh,
how long is this going to go?
-About another seven minutes.
-Yeah, forget it.
-Okay. You got it.
-You're good.
Now, before we start the show,
I did want to open it up
to some audience questions.
Uh. Yes, to those four men
back there.
-What's up, Jalen?
What's up, Jalen?
What's up, big man?
Big fan. Big fan.
Uh, bud, why -- why are you
wearing glasses inside?
-You're right. You're right.
Aye, aye, Captain.
I have a question --
can you foul out of "SNL"?
-No, I-I don't think so.
-So I could be here, like,
the whole show.
Nice!
-All right, who's next?
Uh, Mikal.
-Oh, I have a question.
Are my arms, like, really long?
They're pretty long, right?
-Uh, yeah, buddy.
You got a
great wingspan.
-Yet...I'll never fly.
-Okay.
Uh. Next question.
Uh, OG.
-Remember in Game 4,
when you took that shot
at the end and you missed it?
-Yeah.
-Do you remember
what happened after?
-Yeah, you -- you tipped it in.
-Oh, yeah.
That was awesome.
-Okay, we have time
for just one more question.
Josh.
- Yes. Uh...
Hey, man, I love the podcast.
Uh, is it true that you took
a $113 million pay cut
just to re-sign with the Knicks?
-Uh, yeah, that's pretty true.
- Wow.
Um, so is that money, like,
still up for grabs or...?
-Uh, I don't know, but
I do have a question for you.
Um, why did you do this to me
at the cup ceremony?
-Because it was funny?
Uh, that -- that question
was a layup, bro.
-Yeah, well, the last time
you hit a layup, you did this.
-Fox throws it away!
Josh Hart, ahead of the pack,
lays it up.
Oh! Oh, he missed the layup!
- Hey, bro,
AI be looking so real
these days, bro!
It's crazy!
-All right, well, guys,
can you come up here, please?
We have a great show
for you tonight.
KATSEYE is here.
Stick around.
We'll be right back.
Man, those Pizza Hut sandwiches
really hit the spot, huh?
-Really, yeah.
-Sure did.
But, wait. Uh-oh!
Mark's going in
for the slam dunk! Ahhh!
-Alright, basketball star.
We should probably
get back to work, huh?
-But, wait.
Before we do
looks like Darius
has the ball now.
-Okay, Darius.
-Three seconds left
on the clock.
-Alright.
-He shoots and...
-He misses!
So close, Darius.
-Oh, man.
Yeah, that would have been
awesome.
-Yeah. Feel like we would
have been talking about that
for a long time, buddy.
Anyway, back to work.
What's the status on, uh,
Thompson Park?
-Yeah, we submitted an
application for a federal grant
about a month ago.
-I think NPS is just backed up.
The new regulations are just
too much for them to handle.
-But, wait, guys.
It turns out it wasn't
the last shot of the game.
-What's this, now?
-The referees are saying
there's still
one second left on the clock.
They inbound the ball to Darius.
He shoots and...
-Ohhh! Missed it again!
Sorry, Darius. Looks like the
game is really over this time.
-Yeah. It looks...
It's because the clock ran out.
-Yep.
So, um, is there any way
we can get this NPS thing
speeding along or...?
-I, um,
I have a friend over there.
I can make a call.
-But, wait, though!
-Darius, no.
-You guys are never gonna
believe this.
There's still time on the clock.
-How?
-It turns out
it was daylight savings time.
So there's still two seconds.
-T-That's not
how daylight savings works.
-Well, Darius gets
the ball back for one last shot.
He shoots and...
-Missed again!
And looks like you're all
out of wrappers, so...
- Am I, bitch?
Darius shoots.
-Oh.
-Shoots again.
-One last chance.
-They're not even...
-Eyes closed.
Eyes open.
-Buddy.
-Kobe!
Boom-shakalaka!
-Darius, stop! Stop!
You are embarrassing yourself,
okay?
You're bad at basketball, man.
Can you get that through
your little pea brain
in your big-ass head
that you suck at basketball?
You can't get the ball
in the basket.
Do you get that?
-But there's still one second --
-No, Darius!
There's not one second left,
man.
Stop it, okay?
You're bad at basketball.
-I can't stop.
-Why not, man?
-Because there's something
you guys just don't know.
My name's not Darius Barcelona.
-It's not?
-No.
It's Jalen Brunson.
-Together: Oh, my God!
-That explains why he drives
a neon orange Maserati.
-And why we saw him kissing
Jalen Brunson's wife.
-Well, look,
I only took this job
because ever since
I was a little boy,
I fantasized
about working a modest job...
and hitting a big shot
in front of my coworkers.
-But you're so famous already.
-Just in the NBA.
I don't care about that.
I care about the office.
I want to be known as an --
as an office shooter.
-Yeah, I...
I-I just don't think
that's a great thing to say.
-I can't -- I can't give up now.
Game on the line.
Can't you hear the crowd?
-I think I can!
- Yeah!
Yeah, I hear it, too.
-I can smell the popcorn.
-We believe in you, Jalen.
-Jalen Brunson has the rock.
This one's for all the marbles.
-He leans back.
He shoots.
-All: MVP!
MVP! MVP!
World
Season one
BROUGHT YOU KATSEYE.
NOW BACK TO SEASON TWO, READY TO
FIND OUR NEXT BREAKOUT GIRL
GROUP.
>> AGAIN.
DETAILS.
>> WE'RE ASKING YOURSELVES, CAN
LIGHTNING STRIKE TWICE?
>> I'M NEELSA. 17
AS A KID I PLAYED IN "THE LION KING" ON
BROADWAY.
NOW I WANT TO BE A POP STAR.
>> I'M ISLA, I'M 16.
I'VE BEEN SINGING AND DANCING
SINCE I COULD WALK AND TALK.
>> FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT.
ROLL THE HIPS AND WEAR YOUR
CROWN.
>> GOT IT.
IF I UNDERSTAND CORRECTLY, IT'S
TUMMY, BREAST, TUMMY, BREAST,
PUNCH, BREAST, BUT THEN WHAT?
>> IT WOULD NEVER BE BREAST.
>> I AM DUFF AND I'M A TRIPLE
THREAT.
SWIMMING, DRAWING, AND MAGIC.
>> I'M MARGYLE.
I ONLY WEAR FLIP-FLOPS
BECAUSE I
KEPT PASSING OUT WHEN I TRIED TO
TIE MY SHOES.
CAN SOMEONE HELP ZIP ME UP?
>> IT'S NOT EVEN ON YOU.
>> DUFF AND MARGYLE WITNESSED A
HIT AND RUN
CAUSED BY A MUSIC
EXECUTIVE.
ME.
AND NOW THEY ARE ON THE SHOW.
>> SHE DRAGGED THAT GUY FOR TWO
BLOCKS.
>> WHO CARES?
TBH, I THOUGHT "DREAM ACADEMY"
WAS A SCHOOL WHERE YOU LEARNED
HOW TO CONTROL DREAMS.
BUT SURE, I'LL BE A POP STAR.
>> GIRLS, FOR THE GAME OF THE
FINAL GROUP
WE ARE BETWEEN
FOXTAIL AND TIGRESS.
>> SO CUTE.
WHAT ABOUT MOOSE KNUCKLE?
>> NO.
>> AVATAR SEX?
>> YOU GUYS ARE NOT PICKING THE
NAME.
>> CROW?
CROW?
JUST CROW?
>> IT'S NOT UP FOR DISCUSSION!
>> WHAT'S THAT THING WHERE YOU
MAKE UP YOUR PORNO NAME?
>> FAVORITE FRUIT PLUS THE
STREET YOU GREW UP ON.
>> TOMATO ORPHANAGE.
>> MY MOM WAS IN THE HOSPITAL.
I STARTED SINGING TO MAKE HER
FEEL BETTER.
A DOCTOR FILMED ME SINGING AND
THE VIDEO WENT VIRAL -- OH!
>> I GOT A DREAM I GOT A HAIRCUT
FROM A SPIDER.
IS THAT A GOOD STORY?
>> WE'RE FORMING TEAMS FOR THE
SONGWRITING CHALLENGE.
GROUP "A" WILL BE NILSA, JAMIE,
EMILY.
GROUP "B" WILL BE DUFF, MARGYLE
AND ISLA.
>> OH, GOD.
WELL, I GUESS I'M VISUAL.
>> OKAY, I WAS THINKING
SOMETHING LIKE --
¶ OCEAN WAVES DRIVE ME CRAZY ¶
>> THAT'S GOOD.
I WAS THINKING MAYBE SOMETHING
LIKE --
¶ NEWTON'S CRADLE NEWTON'S
CRADLE ¶
¶ COME AND GET IT NEWTON'S
¶ COME AND GET IT
NEWTON'S CRADLE ¶
¶ COME AND GET IT ¶
>> COME AND GET WHAT?
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M SAYING
THIS.
BUT DUFF AND MARGYLE HAVE REALLY
GROWN ON ME.
THEY'RE LIKE MY BIG SISTERS.
IF MY BIG SISTERS SPOKE
DOTHRAKI.
GUILTY
>> HERE TO ANNOUNCE THE WINNING
GROUP.
OUR "DREAM ACADEMY" SEASON ONE
CHAMPIONS KEFA.
>> WHO ARE THESE LITTLE GIRLS?
>> HEY, ICONS.
WE WERE WOWED BY ALL OF YOU.
>> THE ATHLETICISM.
>> THE TALENT.
>> WHATEVER THIS IS.
>> BUT MORE THAN ANYTHING, YOUR
SONGS.
>> PLEASE ENJOY THE GLOBAL MUSIC
VIDEO DEBUT
OF THE WINNING GIRL
GROUP FEATURING US!
¶ I'M AT THE AMC MATINEE
PUSS 'N' BOOTIN' ¶
¶ I LIKE MY SALADS
HEAVY ON THE CRUTON
CRUTON ¶
¶ I LIKE MY TURTLES TEENAGED
AND A LITTLE MUTANT ¶
¶ I LIKE MY FIGS LIKE
I LIKE MY CRADLE
NEWTON NEWTON ¶
¶ NEWTON'S CRADLE
NEWTON'S CRADLE
COME AND GET IT
NEWTON'S CRADLE ¶
¶ NEWTON'S CRADLE
-Okay. I want to thank you all
for being here.
I know it's tough, but you're
very brave to do this.
And the first step is admitting
that there's a problem.
All right?
Brian, you want to start us off?
-Um, sure. Hi.
I'm Brian. Um.
Oh, man.
It's hard for me to say it.
-It's okay, Brian.
You can do this.
My girl was brought onstage
at the Chris Brown
and Usher tour.
-All: Hi, Brian.
-Oh, uh, so, um, you know,
me and Diane have been married
for three years.
Never had any problems.
And then for our anniversary,
she surprised me
with two front-row tickets
to see Usher and CB.
The show was fun enough.
You know, they're dancing,
and they're ripping open
their shirts and whatnot.
And then six songs in,
"Ursher" jumps off the stage,
dangling a damn cherry...
looking to drop it
in some lady's mouth.
And then, suddenly,
Diane is just hongry as hell!
-Okay, breathe, Brian.
Breathe.
-I'm just saying --
cherries are out of season.
Where did you get that, Ursher?!
-Okay,
let's give Brian a breather.
Uh, you want to go, Philip?
-Uh, sure. Yeah.
Um, I'm Philip.
And my girl was brought onstage
at the Chris Brown
and Usher tour.
-All: Hi, Philip.
-I mean,
I wasn't even at the concert.
I bought tickets for my girl
and her friends.
She gets home,
and I say, "How was it?"
She says, "Fine."
And she goes and takes
a bubble bath with her Theragun.
Next morning, I open TikTok.
I see my girl
strapped to a pole,
spinning like shawarma.
And there's Mr. Breezy,
no shirt on, drenched in sweat.
My girl's eyes roll
in the back of her head
like she's trying
to see her memories.
-Oh, I am so sorry, Philip.
-Video has 123,000 likes.
Top comment says,
"Pray for her man, y'all."
-You got this, man.
-You're strong.
You're strong.
When I spent $1,200
on that meet-and-greet,
I never expected her
to actually greet his meat.
-You're brave, Philip.
You're very brave.
-S-Sorry, I-I have a question.
-Uh, for me?
Sure, Mike. Go ahead.
-If...
If God is real...
why would he create
talented lightskins?
-All right, all right. Easy.
Let's -- Let's --
Let's chill, now.
-Yes, yes, I agree.
Let's move along.
Chris?
-Yeah.
Uh, hi. I'm Chris.
-All: Hi, Chris.
-"Date a Black woman,"
they said.
"It will be fun," they said.
A-And it is.
I loves me a queen.
All I'm saying is...
this kind of stuff don't happen
at the Noah Kahan concert.
-Very right.
Okay. Who's next?
Hi, Dana.
-Hello.
Usher Raymond
dry-humped
my pregnant wife so hard,
she had triplets.
When they came out,
they -- they didn't even cry.
They just went...
♪ Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! ♪
And I was like
"No!"
-Oh, damn you, Ursher!
New generation
-Great game last night, Jake.
You dominated South High.
-Did you see the scouts
in the stands?
You're going straight
to the pros.
-Thanks, guys.
But for me, the "B" in
basketball stands for brothers.
-We're a team!
-Um, sorry.
Uh, I just transferred here,
and I was wondering
if I could maybe join you guys?
-Sorry, bud. We're full up.
-Yeah. Kick rocks, dude.
-Well, thanks, anyway.
-Guys. Whoa!
Everyone deserves a shot.
What's up, man?
I'm Jake.
Of course you can ball with us.
But know this.
Here at North High,
you got to give it all you got.
-Oh, yeah.
This is gonna be good. Ha ha!
-♪ On this team,
we give it our all ♪
♪ Yeah, you best believe
this is basketball ♪
♪ Pass me the ball,
nothing but net ♪
♪ Get in your face
and then I fake left ♪
♪ Got what it takes ♪
♪ I ain't started yet ♪
♪ 'Cause this is basketba-a-ll ♪
♪ Pass it to me
and I know what I got ♪
♪ Put the team on my back,
then I take the shot ♪
Okay, no problem.
♪ Take the shot ♪
Please.
Just please.
Oh, my God!
-Jake! Jake!
All right, Mr. New Guy,
good blocks.
But basketball isn't
just about defense.
It's about heart.
Come on, guys.
Let's show him how it's done.
♪ T-E-A-M ♪
♪ I got my ball
and I got my -- ♪
Okay, game on.
-Oh, my ankles!
-Excuse me.
Chase the ball.
-I'm trying.
-Call me daddy now.
-Where did you come from?!
-Yo, that was lit as hell, bro!
-Derrick, I've never heard you
talk like that.
-I didn't know basketball
could, like, be not gay.
-Jake, what are we supposed
to do?
You're our best player.
-I know, but maybe...
not anymore.
♪ Ever since
I was a little boy ♪
Oh! Oh, stop! Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Aah! Why?!
Just give me 30 seconds
to get on my feet, please!
Please! God!
This is actually a good time
to tell you guys
I don't even care
about basketball anymore.
-That's right.
I've decided I'm doing
the musical
because I've fallen in love.
-Jake!
-Jessiciah.
♪ The look in your eyes
when we're together ♪
-♪ This crazy love will be
with us forever ♪
-♪ A rose like you
only blooms so unique ♪
-What the hell?
-♪ Baby, let's come together,
'cause this is meant to be ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Not him, but me ♪
-Yeah, I think I'm gonna hook up
with this guy.
-Stop, stop.
I see that.
But, hey, before you do
bucket!
-Hello?
We -- no, I can hear you now.
Yes, yes. My father was admitted
last night.
He fell.
I'm trying to reach
his hospital room.
No, no, no, don't! Oh, my God.
They put me on hold again.
-It'll be fine, honey.
They'll rebook us
on another flight soon.
-My dad is in the hospital,
Clark.
I need to get home now!
Oh, we should have flown Delta.
But you wanted to save money
and bought tickets
on a janky airline.
-Okay, look. Aye, Chihuahua
Airlines is not janky.
-Yes, yes. Hello? I-I'm here.
Can you update me on
my father's condition, please?
Oh! David!
These massage chairs are a
game-changer for business trips.
I don't want this layover
to end, David!
-Oh! Oh.
Oh, amen, Patrick.
-Oh, David!
The deep-tissue setting
is destroying my knot, David.
Oh!
-Ride it out, Patrick.
-No. I'm -- I'm sorry.
It's a little loud here.
Can you repeat that?
-Patrick, this rolling mode
is devastating me.
-I know.
The roll is harder
than the deep tissue, David.
It's headed straight
for my big knot, David.
I'm scared, David!
-Be brave, Patrick.
-David!
-No, no. No, I'm not making
those sounds.
It's two men in massage chairs.
-I'm sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry.
What-- what did you say?
So, is he responsive or no?
-Oh, my God!
-Oh. Oh, hell, yes!
-Yeah!
-Hey! Hey!
What the hell is going on
with your porno moans?
This is the Denver airport,
not a bedroom.
-Oh, I-I wasn't even aware I
was making sounds. I apologize.
-We're on a work trip,
and we've been on cramped regional
connecting flights all day, sir.
-Oof!
We did Boston to Pittsburgh...
-Pittsburgh to Providence...
-Then Providence to Denver.
Our last one was Denver
to Tampa Bay.
-Yeah.
-That is the worst route
I've ever heard in my life.
Look, you can enjoy the chairs.
Just stop the moaning.
We're getting complaints
from the women
in the weird breastfeeding
shed.
-David, David.
it's changing to chop, David.
Oh, hell, yes!
Oh, God, yes!
-Oh! Ahh! David.
It's...it's...
it's too much for me!
David, look at me!
-I can't, Patrick.
-Look at me in the eye,
David!
-I can't, Patrick.
-Look at me, David!
-I can't.
-David, it's gonna break me!
Ah!
-Let it break you, Patrick.
-David!
-Okay, can you lower
the volume, please?
The hospital hung up on me
because they thought
I was having sex.
-Yeah, and we weren't,
and we haven't in a while.
-Sorry, ma'am.
We're just relieving tension.
Ah! David, what intensity
setting are you on?
-Uh! Harder, D-d-daddy.
Harder, Daddy.
What? What about you?
-I don't know, David.
I think mine's higher.
It says Prison Beating.
David?! David?! David?!
David?! David?!
-Don't touch me!
-David?! David?!
-Oh, how do you feel, David?
-Turned...out.
-Oh.
-Oh, you both are disgusting!
-Disgusting?
It's a massage. It's not sexual.
-All right, let's go. Get up.
Well, at least wait
for our erections to go down.
-Ladies and gentlemen,
KATSEYE.
Animal
-♪ You're the boss ♪
♪ You run the circus, baby ♪
♪ Take it up a notch ♪
♪ You're so sophisticated ♪
♪ Don't wanna be on a schedule ♪
♪ You're on your own time ♪
-♪ Off the scale
that goes from hot to crazy ♪
♪ Fingernails --
one, two, three colors painted ♪
♪ Crop top and baggy jeans,
holding your waistline ♪
-♪ You make the light
and the shadows collide ♪
♪ Your body gets twisted
and tangled in mine ♪
♪ Love so good ♪
♪ How could this be free? ♪
♪ I'll keep your secret
safe with me ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪
-♪ I'll be gone by morning ♪
♪ So getcha, getcha heels
on the floor, then ♪
♪ So, are you with me? ♪
-♪ Are you with me? ♪
-♪ Be careful what you're wishing for ♪
♪ 'Cause I get freaky ♪
-♪ You make the light
and the shadows collide ♪
♪ Your body gets twisted
and tangled in mine ♪
♪ Love so good ♪
♪ How could this be free? ♪
♪ I keep your secret
safe with me ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪
-♪ I'm gettin' overwhelmed ♪
♪ R-R-Right now ♪
♪ Want you to give it to me
all night long ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪
-♪ Nobody knows
you're out of control ♪
♪ But I see a side
behind the closed doors ♪
♪ They get a glimpse
here on the dance floor ♪
♪ You move like an animal ♪